It's so weird.
How did Joey end up kissing
Charlie last night?
I thought you'd end up
kissing Charlie.
Hey, I thought I'd end up
kissing Charlie, too, okay?
But surprise!
I missed most of the party.
Charlie's a girl, right?
Yes, she's this new professor
in my department
that I did not kiss.
I don't know why Joey
had to kiss her.
I mean, of all the girls
at the party, God!
Why do you care so much?
Yes, Rachel...
why do you
care so much?
Because Ross is the father
of my child... you know,
and I want him to hook up
with lots of women.
Look, I just,
all I'm saying
is I don't think
that Joey and Charlie
have anything in common.
I don't know, they seemed
to have a shared interest
in each other's tonsils.
Wow. Joey and a professor.
Can you imagine
if they had kids?
And if the kids got
her intelligence
and Joey's raw sexual magnetism?
Those nerds would get laid.
All right, so, Ross,
you're okay with all this?
Yeah, it's no big deal.
I mean, I just met her.
I'm fine with it.
Oh, I forgot how hot she was.
I'm going to get
some more coffee.
Oh, you know,
I'll come with you.
Okay.
So, a professor, huh?
Yeah.
She is cool.
And she's so smart.
Her mind is totally acrimonious.
Guess that's not how
she used it.
I feel like I owe you
an explanation.
I don't ordinarily go around
kissing guys at parties.
I'm, uh...
well, I'm kind
of embarrassed.
I really hope you don't
think less of me.
Think less of you? No.
I don't think
less of you.
I mean, you saw someone you
liked and you kissed them.
Those people
who like someone
and don't kiss them,
those people are stupid.
I hate those people.
You know, actually,
I'm a little surprised
at myself.
I mean, Joey is so different
from the guys I usually date.
I mean, they're all
professors, intellectuals,
paleontologists mostly.
You know, very cerebral...
Yeah, I know the type.
Hey, if we want
to grab a bite
before work,
we'd better
get acrimonious.
No?
Am I getting
close?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
RACHEL:
Hi.
Hey, you guys,
look what I just got.
RACHEL:
Oh, wow,
I love those.
Where did you get them?
I bought them off eBay.
They used to belong
to the late Shania Twain.
Phoebe, Shania Twain
is still alive.
Oh, then I overpaid.
Hey, what's this?
Oh, it's a gift certificate
to this new spa in Soho.
Well, you can't show
Phoebe this.
She hates those
corporate massage chains.
Oh, now I can't get a massage?
There are so many things
that she disapproves of.
I can't eat veal.
I can't wear fur.
I can't go hunting.
Do you want to go hunting?
Well, I would like
to have the option.
Oh, what's that?
Hey, Rachel.
What?
No, you can't go there.
You know how I feel about
these big massage places.
They're putting people like me
out of business.
And she wants
to go hunting, too.
Phoebe, come on,
I don't want to waste it.
It would be like throwing away
a hundred bucks.
Okay, this is not about
the money, okay?
It's about... it's about
corporate greed
destroying our hearts
and leaving us hollow shells.
I don't care about any of that.
Well, do you care about
friendship?
I feel really strongly
about this, Rachel.
Please don't use
this gift certificate.
I'm asking you as a friend.
Oh, not as a friend,
Phoebe...
Fine, I won't use it.
Promise?
I promise.
Thank you.
Well, I am going hunting.
Hey, honey.
I missed you today.
Oh, yeah?
What do you want
to do tonight?
Oh, well,
maybe we could, uh...
Okay, trying to turn me on
by making a mess?
Know your audience.
Besides, tomorrow we're doing
those fertility tests.
And until then,
you need to keep
your tadpoles in the tank.
Do we really need
to take those tests?
Honey, we've been trying
to have a baby for over a year.
I just think it's a good idea
to find out
if everything's okay.
Just a few routine tests.
But I don't want
to do it in a cup.
What is the big deal?
It's weird.
You're in a doctor's office.
It's not okay to do it
in a doctor's office,
but it is okay to do it in a
parked car behind a Taco Bell?
I cannot believe Ross
told you that.
And in my defense,
it was a Wendy's.
Look, I don't want
to do these tests either,
but I really do think
it's a good idea.
Yeah, okay, I'm sure a doctor's
office can't be worse
than on a class trip
to the Hershey factory.
( gasps )
Oh, yeah!
Rachel talks, too!
Who says wine has to cost
more than milk?
( knocking at door )
Hey.
Hi.
Come on in.
How are you?
I'm good.
Can I offer you a drink?
Please.
I have been crazed all day.
I had a meeting with the dean,
and my syllabus
for summer school is due,
and I'm writing the foreword
for a friend's book.
Yeah, I had a pretty
hectic day at work, too.
Today I had to open
a door and go...
( gasps )
So I am just
so excited to be here.
I mean, I cannot wait
to start exploring the city.
Hey, if you need
a tour guide...
Oh, you mean it?
That would be so fun.
Oh, yeah,
definitely.
Definitely, okay.
Uh, what do you want
to see first?
Uh, well...
we could go see
the Kronos Quartet
at Avery Fisher Hall.
Okay.
And, uh...
Oh, there's a collection of
Walt Whitman letters on display
at the public library.
I know.
But first,
I have to see the Met.
Okay, let me stop you
right there.
The Mets suck, okay?
You want to see
the Yankees.
No, no, not the Mets.
The Met. Singular.
Which one? They all suck.
The museum.
I don't think so.
Hi, there.
Hello.
( calm tone ):
Welcome to Lavender Day Spa.
How may I help you?
Um, hi.
I have a massage appointment
under Rachel Green.
And here is my gift certificate.
This has been torn up.
And taped back together.
Okay, well, I'll call you
as soon as your massage
therapist is ready.
Okay.
Have a seat through
the glass doors.
( calm tone ):
Through the glass doors.
( same tone ):
All righty then.
Phoebe,
your next client's
in the waiting room.
Okay.
Do we have to talk like that
when they're not around?
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
Listen...
is there someone who
can fill in for me?
Sorry, everyone is booked.
But that woman can't
know that I work here.
She's a friend of mine
and I made this big stink
about how awful
these massage chains are.
Then why do you work here?
Because it's good money.
But that doesn't change the fact
that this is an evil,
bloodsucking corporate machine.
Well, I think this
is a great place to work.
( whispering ):
Are they listening?
Ross, hey.
Hi.
I, uh... I need to talk
to you about Charlie.
Oh, do you?
Do you really?
Yeah, I'm kind of having
a little problem.
Look, if you don't know what
the word "acrimonious" means
just don't use it.
No, look.
You know Charlie, right?
She's cool, she's funny.
Her body is so...
Get to the problem.
Right.
She's just so much smarter
than all the girls
I've ever dated.
Combined.
You know, and I just...
I don't want her
to think I'm stupid.
Are you wearing two belts?
Hey, what do you know?
You were saying you didn't
want to seem stupid.
Right, right, right.
Well, she... like,
she wants to go
to all these cultural places
and I don't know how to
talk about that stuff.
You got to help me out.
You know, I really don't
want to get involved
in your guys' relationship.
Oh, dude, please.
Come on.
You're the smartest
person I know.
And I really like this girl.
I don't want to lose her.
Fine.
Thanks.
Okay, let's see.
Oh-- you should take her
to the Met.
The Mets.
No, no, no. The Met.
The Metropolitan Museum of Art.
Oh, that's what she meant.
You know what, if
they're gonna shorten it
they should call it
the "Muse," you know,
short for "museum" and
avoid all the confusion.
Yeah, yeah, most days
the place is packed
with confused,
angry baseball fans.
Okay.
All right, so I'll
take her to the Met.
Yeah.
Ooh, ooh, okay.
There's this great
rare bookstore
on Madison Avenue.
You know what,
she loves architecture.
You know what you should do?
You should take
a walk down Fifth
to the St. Patrick's Cathedral.
And there, there's this
great little pastry shop
that she'd love.
Geez, Ross, sounds like you
should be going on this date.
But I'm not.
And you know what?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
You're going
way too fast, okay?
Go back to the Met.
You got to tell me
exactly what to do there.
Okay, when you walk into
the museum, take a right.
That's the antiquities wing.
Ancient Egypt, Mesopotamia
up to the Byzantine Empire.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Okay, so I walk in the
door, I make a right.
I have a weird feeling
about this place.
How do I know
they're not going
to secretly videotape me
and put it all over
the Internet?
Because, honey--
and I mean this in the
sweetest way possible--
nobody's going to want
to watch that.
Mr. Bing,
here you are.
You'll go into that room
and deposit your specimen
into the container.
Deposit my specimen.
You know, I usually have
to call a 900 number
for that kind of talk.
Thanks. Got it.
All right, honey,
my tests are down
the hall.
Are you sure you're
going to be okay?
Yeah, I guess.
Look, I know this is
embarrassing,
but nobody cares.
No one here even knows you.
Oh...
my... God!
Oh, come on!
( braying laughter )
How great is this?
We're probably fertile.
Let's go home.
Why are you here?
Well, Sid and I
are trying again,
and we had trouble
last time,
because apparently...
No, no, no, I mean,
why, why is she here?
Oh, someone's
a little cranky today
'cause they have
to do it in a cup.
Oh, they gave you
the kiddie size.
What?
( braying laughter )
This, this was fun,
but I've got an invasive
vaginal exam to get to.
I'd love to stay,
but I've got a hot date.
Please, go.
Just let me know
if you need a hand.
( laughs )
I think it just fell off.
( Swedish accent ):
Hello, ya.
It's time for your massage, ya.
Put your face in the hole.
Well, a Swedish massage
from a real Swedish person.
Okay, then I'm Swedish.
So, what's your name?
It's a normal
Swedish name-- Ikea.
Whoa, what an
interesting name.
Ya.
You know, I kind of...
Time for your scalp massage.
Wow,
I really love your...
( gasps )
Is something wrong?
No, it just, um...
it feels so good, Ikea.
Hey, say, you'll
know this.
What's the capital
of Sweden?
Um, Stockholm.
Damn, I wish I knew
if that was right.
Note the painterly lines
and subtle impasto
on this canvas.
Monet painted quickly
and usually outdoors
as his elusive subject
was light itself.
Do you have any idea
what you just said?
No, no. My mouth says
the words,
my brain is thinking
monster trucks.
Okay, now remember,
when you get to the museum,
Monet is not spelled M-O-N-A-Y.
I wrote that out phonetically
for you.
Phonetically?
Yeah, yeah, that mea--
You know, we don't have time
for this, okay.
But I got to say,
I'm really impressed
that you were able
to memorize all this so quickly.
I'm an actor.
I can memorize anything.
Last week on Days
I had to say
"Frontal temporal
zygomatic craniotomy."
Wow. What does that mean?
No idea.
But the guy I said it to
dies in the next scene,
so I guess it means
you're going to get
eaten by a bear.
Okay.
Um, so let's move on
to the Renaissance.
Okay.
Caravaggio uses
chiaroscuro here
to highlight the anguish
of the central figure.
Touch it.
It's really bumpy.
Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
No, no, no.
No ad-libbing,
and, dude,
you can't touch
the paintings.
Come on.
No!
My specimen's in the room.
And I just want to thank
whoever knocked on the door
while I was in there.
Really helps speed
the process along.
Janice...
you're not gone?
Oh, Sid is still in his room.
I don't allow porn at home,
so this is like a vacation
for him.
( laughs )
So, did you do it?
Did you make your deposit?
Yeah, yeah. Hard part's over.
That's not the
hard part, honey.
The hard part
is what comes next.
Aren't you a little worried
about the results?
I haven't even thought
about the results.
I just assumed everything
was going to be okay.
Oh, well, you know what?
It probably is.
Yeah, but what if
it's not?
What if there's a reason
we can't have a baby?
Oh, Chandler, look,
you and Monica are meant
to have children.
I'm sure it's going
to be just fine.
Yeah, yeah, okay. Thanks.
I can't believe
I didn't even think of that.
I guess I was so worried
about having to come here
and do that.
You can do it
in the parking lot
of a Taco Bell,
but you can't do it
at a doctor's office?
It was a Wendy's!
( Swedish accent ):
♪ Eepan, streepan,
gloopy, gloppy. ♪
And that's the Swedish
national anthem.
Thank you for asking.
Wow, Ikea,
what a rich culture.
Um, you know what?
I have a friend
who's a masseuse.
Oh, ya, ya?
Ya. She's not very good,
though.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
And why do you think that is?
I don't know.
Maybe it's
because she's got
such callus-y fingers
from playing crummy guitar.
( feigned laughter )
Or, maybe she has trouble
loosening your knots
because you're such
a high-maintenance tight ass.
Phoebe!
You know it's me?
Well, for like
a half an hour.
Man, you can lie about Sweden.
How-how can you come here?
How could you not tell me
you worked here?!
I don't have to tell you
everything.
Yes, you do
if you're going
to make me feel guilty
for getting a free massage.
Tip's not included.
Oh!
Phoebe, why
did you lie to me
about working here?
Because I was ashamed, okay?
I sold out for the cash.
And they give me benefits
like medical and dental
and a four-oh-wunk.
But, you know, you pay a price.
Now I'm this corporate stooge
and-and punching a clock, and...
( groans with disgust):
paying taxes.
Phoebe, honey,
if you hate it so much,
you should walk out there
right now and quit.
Be true to what
you believe in.
Honey, you have principles
and I so admire that.
I don't have any!
You know what?
You're right.
I am going to quit.
It's time I took my life back.
Good for you,
Pheebs.
Okay.
( whispering ):
If you guys have microphones
in there, too,
I didn't mean any of that.
I love you.
Aha! Gotcha.
Die! Die!
Die!
"Respectively,
Professor R. Geller."
Hey.
Hi.
Hey, how was the Met?
Oh, the museum was amazing.
Yeah?
Yeah, Joey really
knows his art, huh?
Not so much, no.
He had clearly memorized
all this stuff to say
and some of it didn't
even make any sense.
What do you mean?
Well, for one,
he was talking
about paintings
that were nowhere around.
Wait a minute. Wh...?
When you guys
walked into the Met,
did-did you go to the right?
No, we went to the left.
Oh, Joey, Joey, Joey.
Well, still, I mean,
seems like you guys are having
a great time together.
Yeah...
Yeah, it's fun.
What?
Uh, actually, you know,
Joey's your friend
and-and you don't really
know me that well.
It would be weird.
Well, I mean, a little,
but no, what, go on.
Well, um,
I'm just thinking that maybe
Joey isn't the right guy
for me to be with right now.
You know, maybe
I should...
be with someone...
( sighs )
...I have more
in common with.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Well, but you know what?
Um... I don't know,
I think you should give Joey
a chance.
I mean,
he's a great guy.
And sure, he doesn't know
that much about art,
but, you know, you could
always talk about that
with someone else.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
And if you
think about it,
I mean, the reason he memorized
all that stuff,
because he thought
it was important to you.
You know, that's the kind
of guy Joey is.
He is very sweet.
Plus he is hot!
That-that was going to be
my next argument.
Hey.
You ready?
Yeah, let's go.
Wow.
( giggling )
CHARLIE:
Thanks, Ross.
Yep.
JOEY:
Hey, Ross.
That art stuff worked.
You hooked me up.
Glad I could help, man.
Although some of the stuff
wasn't where you said it was
going to be, but I made it work.
It is not okay that I am aroused
by this now.
( phone rings )
Hello?
Oh, hi, Dr. Connelly.
Uh, no, well, she's not here,
but, uh, you know,
I can tell her.
Should I be sitting down
for this?
Oh.
Uh-huh.
Well, so, what does that mean?
Okay. Uh... okay, thank you.
Thanks.
Hey, sweetie.
Dr. Connelly just called.
Oh, with good news?
Of course
it's not good news.
You just said
"Dr. Connelly just called."
If it was good news
you would have said,
"Dr. Connelly
just called!"
But, um, so,
what-what is it?
Is it, um...
is there a problem?
Is there a problem
with me or... or with you?
Actually, it's both of us.
What?
Apparently, my sperm
have low motility
and you have an
"inhospitable
environment."
Oh.
Well, uh,
what does that mean?
It means that my guys won't
get off their Barcaloungers
and you have a uterus
that is prepared to
kill the ones that do.
It means...
Chandler...
It means that we
can keep trying.
But there's a good chance
this may never happen for us.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
( sniffling )
Well...
Well, we're going
to figure this out.
Yeah.
I know.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Good morning, Phoebe.
Good morning, receptionist.
Here's your schedule
for the day.
Your first client
is in room number one.
"R... Rachel Green."
Son of a bitch!
She came back?!
( scoffs )
( Scottish accent ):
Are you ready
for your Scottish massage?
Put your face in the hole,
lassie.